usfiainc.com 2015-06-20

# Privacy Policy

                                 Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for
(www.usfiainc.com). This privacy notice applies solely to information
collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
    1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through
       the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
    2. The choices available to you regarding the use of your data.
    3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your
       information.
    4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only
have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or
other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to
anyone.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.
You may also contact us anytime to check/update your current data, make
changes/corrections to your data, delete your current data, and/or to
express any concern you have about the use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive
information via the website, your information is protected both online and
offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data),
that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can
verify this by looking for “                ” a closed lock icon at the bottom of
your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of
the web page.

                        隐私权保密措施
此隐私权声明概述了当您游览 www.usfiainc.com 时，您的隐私权保护措施。详细如下：
  1. 当您游览我们的网页时，您所提供的个人资料，它是如何使用及和谁共享。
  2. 当您的资料使用时，可提供的选择。
  3. 确保您的个人资料被滥用的安全程序。
  4. 如何更正不准确的个人信息。
资料收集，使用和共享
当您游览本网站 (www.usfiainc.com) 时，我们是您提供个人信息的唯一对象。我们只
存取或收集您在自愿的情况下，通过电子邮件或其他直接联系方式提供的个人信息。绝不
涉及任何买卖及租借您个人资料行为。
关于您个人资料的使用及掌控
您随时享有掌控个人资料的自由。联系我们关于：
     - 咨询,更新，删除，询问我们收集的任何有关您的资料。
安全措施
我们采取预防措施来保护您的资料。当您通过我们的网站提供敏感讯息时，无论是在线或
离线的情况下，您的资料将会被保密。
当收集您的敏感资料时（列如信用卡资料等），您所提供的资料将通过加密且安全的方式
传送。当您在网页地址栏上看到 “https” 的字眼或当您看到一个 “           “的
图形时，您就可以确定您所提供的资料是通过加密且安全的方式传送。
